<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changsheng Quan</title><link>https://quancs.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Changsheng Quan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quancs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Narrow-band Deep Speech Separation</title><link>https://quancs.github.io/blog/nbss/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quancs.github.io/blog/nbss/</guid><description>Abstract [1] Changsheng Quan, Xiaofei Li. Multi-channel Narrow-band Deep Speech Separation with Full-band Permutation Invariant Training. In ICASSP 2022. [Code], [Pdf], [Results], [Examples]
This paper addresses the problem of multi-channel multi-speech separation based on deep learning techniques. In the short time Fourier transform domain, we propose an end-to-end narrow-band network that directly takes as input the multi-channel mixture signals of one frequency, and outputs the separated signals of this frequency.</description></item><item><title>Publication</title><link>https://quancs.github.io/publication/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quancs.github.io/publication/</guid><description>2021 [4] Changsheng Quan and Xiaofei Li. 2021. Multi-channel Narrow-Band Deep Speech Separation with Full-band Permutation Invariant Training. arXiv preprint arXiv:2110.05966 (2021). [examples and introduction] [code] [pdf]
[3] Changsheng Quan and Ping Guo. 2021. A local search method based on edge age strategy for minimum vertex cover problem in massive graphs. Expert Systems with Applications 182, (November 2021), 115185. DOI:https://doi.org/10.1016/j.eswa.2021.115185 [code]
2019 [2] Ping Guo, Changsheng Quan, and Haizhu Chen. 2019.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://quancs.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quancs.github.io/about/</guid><description>Personal Profile I am a joint Ph.D. student of Westlake University and Zhejiang University, advised by Dr. Xiaofei Li. Also, I am a member of Audio Laboratory in Westlake University, where I do my research work on Machine Learning, and Speech Separation.
Research My research interests include Machine Learning and Audio Signal Processing. Especially in, Speech Separation, Enhancement, ASR.
More Github, Google Scholar</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://quancs.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quancs.github.io/contact/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>